{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600910358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600910358"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 780e643e-3ef6-4dc6-a0b4-cbeec8832535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600921296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600921296"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 780e643e-3ef6-4dc6-a0b4-cbeec8832535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600928838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600928838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" b967f707-481f-4eb4-bdb0-651de778d385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600945765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600945765"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" b967f707-481f-4eb4-bdb0-651de778d385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600948362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600948361"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" b967f707-481f-4eb4-bdb0-651de778d385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600948490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600948490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" b967f707-481f-4eb4-bdb0-651de778d385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600957989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600957989"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" d1a26794-1974-4670-821d-d14c8d961a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600970831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600970830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" d1a26794-1974-4670-821d-d14c8d961a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600973516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600973515"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" d1a26794-1974-4670-821d-d14c8d961a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600973627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600973627"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" d1a26794-1974-4670-821d-d14c8d961a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600983930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600983930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600984304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600984303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600984794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600984793"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600985145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600985145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600985560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600985560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600986044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600986043"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600986272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600986272"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600989460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600989459"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600989498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600989497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600990223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600990222"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600990624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600990623"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600990923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600990922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600991139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600991138"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600991343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600991342"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600991671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600991670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600991906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600991905"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600995109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600995108"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600995520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600995519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600998146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600998145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600998359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600998359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548600998571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548600998570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601002094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601002093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601005843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601005843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601006875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601006874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601009633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601009632"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601010026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601010026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601010519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601010519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601010869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601010868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601011281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601011280"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601011767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601011767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601012000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601012000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601015207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601015206"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601015247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601015246"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601015974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601015973"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601016378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601016378"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601016681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601016681"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601016897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601016896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601017102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601017101"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601017435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601017434"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601017667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601017666"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601020315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601020313"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601020399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601020399"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 721c03db-8d00-4ecb-a5db-e2f28c104041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601054915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601054915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huu-hadithi-nani-wale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" wale"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601062320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601062320"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huu-hadithi-nani-wale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601089602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601089602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_lake-nani-je-kimya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601119468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601119468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_baridi-pumzi-gari-vya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" pumzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601123983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601123983"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_baridi-pumzi-gari-vya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601139948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601139947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gari_baridi-pumzi-gari-vya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601140087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601140087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601153641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601153641"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601159968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601159968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 37fb310e-1b39-4eae-b2f5-d13557751c3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601170363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601170363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_A-E-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601174881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601174881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-E-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601179271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601179270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_U-J-D"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601183782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601183782"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_R-J-N"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601188170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601188170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_K-O-J"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601192347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601192347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-W-P"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601198126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601198126"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601202301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601202301"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_P-E-J"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601206735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601206735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_M-N-J"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601209960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601209960"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601215710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601215709"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 7f5863a4-2522-4bba-8a1f-867e335fd7b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601279529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601279528"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_hadithi-baridi-upepo-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601282735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601282735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_hadithi-baridi-upepo-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601320100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601320100"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_hadithi-baba-upepo-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601387131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601387131"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baridi-hata-upepo-jua"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601448420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601448420"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-huyo-njaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601451720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601451720"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-huyo-njaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601455773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601455773"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-huyo-njaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601492691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601492691"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baba-kubwa-upepo-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601496436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601496436"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baba-kubwa-upepo-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601512066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601512066"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baba-kubwa-upepo-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601551324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601551324"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_nani-baridi-upepo-shule"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" baridi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601556344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601556343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_nani-baridi-upepo-shule"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601612076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601612076"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-lake-baridi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" baridi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601615188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601615188"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-lake-baridi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" lake"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601618138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601618138"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-lake-baridi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601622430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601622430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-lake-baridi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601632022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601632015"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baba-lake-baridi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601632142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601632142"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601645407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601645406"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 6bd232de-f850-427a-b5b9-d97581fd9c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601645485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601645485"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 5dea3cfa-db18-4d80-9319-b852d61a2841"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601653017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601653017"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 5dea3cfa-db18-4d80-9319-b852d61a2841"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601755975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601755975"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 12bbaed4-c33f-4f4c-b8c2-caa213006b63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601761801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601761801"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 12bbaed4-c33f-4f4c-b8c2-caa213006b63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601771758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601771757"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 12bbaed4-c33f-4f4c-b8c2-caa213006b63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601788433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601788433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 12bbaed4-c33f-4f4c-b8c2-caa213006b63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601798025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601798025"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 12bbaed4-c33f-4f4c-b8c2-caa213006b63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601810772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601810772"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601811956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601811956"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601812858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601812857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601813931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601813931"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601814936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601814936"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601815792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601815792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601816897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601816896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601817568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601817568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601818866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601818866"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601821397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601821397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601821586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601821586"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601822567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601822566"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601823944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601823943"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601824087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601824087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601825247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601825246"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601825906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601825906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601827004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601827003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601827799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601827799"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601827923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601827922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601828624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601828623"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601831570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601831570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601832453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601832452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601832683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601832683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601833314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601833313"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601833428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601833427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601834432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601834432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601835344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601835343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601836038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601836038"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601837324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601837323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601839974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601839974"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601841015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601841014"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601841212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601841212"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601841935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601841935"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601842952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601842952"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601843962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601843962"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601844713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601844712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601845311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601845310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601846176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601846175"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601846691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601846690"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601847544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601847532"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601850947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601850947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601851635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601851635"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601852453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601852452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601853605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601853604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601854263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601854262"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601854916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601854916"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601855623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601855623"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601856560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601856559"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601857456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601857455"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601857702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601857702"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601858998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601858998"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601859589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601859589"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601862151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601862150"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601862492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601862491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601863246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601863246"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601864907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601864906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601865391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601865391"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601865906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601865906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601866397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601866397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601869583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601869583"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601870255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601870254"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601871717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601871717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601872342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601872339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601872956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601872938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601873655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601873655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601874082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601874081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601875090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601875089"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601878092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601878092"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601879077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601879077"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601880083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601880082"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601880604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601880603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601880777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601880777"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601882001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601882000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601883405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601883405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601883650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601883650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601884774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601884774"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601885338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601885338"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601888356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601888356"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601889310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601889310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601890034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601890034"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601890927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601890927"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601892878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601892878"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601892929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601892929"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 1ad21d22-98e3-4153-bf0e-7e7ec4f43473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601907145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601907145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601911607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601911607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601918432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601918432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601923373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601923373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601928417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601928417"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601931577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601931577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601935500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601935500"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601948876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601948876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601954991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601954991"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601971024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601971024"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601973683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601973682"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601979832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601979832"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548601989265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548601989265"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190127_175500"," gameId":" 04f8e9f4-3aa4-4252-bc54-7512f03c81b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}